I'm Peppa Pig. [grunts]
-This is my little brother George.
-[grunting]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[grunts]
-And this is Daddy Pig.
[laugh]
Peppa Pig. [grunts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is playtime at school.
Peppa and her friends
are running around, having fun.
Ow! That hurts.
Are you all right, Peppa?
I've hurt my knee.
[squeaks] Madame Gazelle,
Peppa has fallen over.
You've just grazed your knee, Peppa.
First Madame Gazelle cleans Peppa's knee.
Then she puts a plaster on it.
-Does that feel any better?
-Yes. Thank you.
Now, children, you may have noticed
that Pedro Pony isn't here today.
Is he late again?
No, Suzy. Pedro is in hospital.
[in unison] Ooh.
And today we are going to visit him.
This is the hospital.
Peppa and her friends have come
to visit Pedro Pony.
Remember, children, stay close to me.
I don't want you getting lost.
[in unison] Yes, Madame Gazelle.
Excuse me, Mr. Bull,
which way is the children's ward?
Down the steps, double doors,
right, left, right, along the corridor,
up the stairs, third on your left.
-Ah.
-Or you could just take the lift.
[laughing]
[Mr. Bull] Children's ward.
[bleats] Pedro will be asleep.
Sick people do a lot of sleeping.
Hello, everyone.
[in unison] Hello, Pedro.
Why aren't you asleep?
You don't look sick.
I broke my leg,
and they put it in this plaster cast.
[all] Wow!
The plaster cast helps
Pedro's leg get better.
I grazed my knee,
and I got a plaster, too.
Wow.
Do you want to draw on my plaster cast?
Yes, please.
The children are all doing drawings
on Pedro's plaster cast.
[Danny] I'm drawing a football.
[Emily] I've drawn some flowers.
[Rebecca] Mr. Potato.
[Suzy] A parrot.
[Peppa] And I've drawn a muddy puddle.
Wow, thanks, everyone.
You can draw on my plaster, too.
Okay. I'll draw a little flower.
Thank you, Pedro.
Pedro, what's it like being in hospital?
It's great.
[whispers] What are the nurses like?
They give me stickers.
[all] Wow.
And they come
whenever I press this button.
[buzzes]
Who's that? I wonder.
Could it be Pedro?
What do you want, Pedro? We are very busy.
I've got a bit of an itch.
Even if your leg is itching,
we can't take the cast off
until your leg is better.
It's not my leg that's itching.
It's my ear.
Is that better?
Yes, thank you. [giggles]
Lunchtime.
What would you like to eat today, Pedro?
Can I have spaghetti
and sponge pudding, please?
You get your dinner in bed?
Yes. [giggles]
Mm. That looks tasty.
Dr. Brown Bear has come
to see how Pedro is doing.
How are we today, Pedro?
My ear is a bit itchy, just here.
Mm. I'd say you're almost better.
[giggles]
[dings]
Visiting time is over.
[in unison] Bye, Pedro.
Bye, everyone.
Get well soon, Pedro.
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
[clamoring]
It is another school day.
Peppa and her friends are playing
in the playground.
Madame Gazelle, my plaster has fallen off.
Can I have another one?
You don't need a plaster, Peppa.
Your knee is better.
Oh, yes. [giggles]
Hello, everyone.
Pedro Pony is back.
Oh, hello, Pedro.
Where's your plaster cast?
They took it off because my leg is better.
Is your leg stronger now?
It's stronger than it was before.
It's a super leg.
Can you run on it?
Watch this.
[neighs and giggles]
Pedro likes running around, having fun.
Everybody likes running around,
having fun.
[all giggling]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is springtime.
Grandpa Pig has made a chocolate egg hunt.
Is everybody ready?
No, Grandpa. Freddy Fox isn't here.
[horn honks]
[barks] Hello, everyone.
Hello, Freddy.
Ah. Hello, Mr. Fox. Are you staying?
I wish I could.
I loved egg hunts when I was a little lad.
-See you later, Freddy.
-[barks]
Now, are we ready for the egg hunt?
[in unison] Yes, Grandpa Pig.
There are lots of chocolate eggs hidden
in my garden.
You must find them.
Easy.
[grunts] But be careful not
to step on my little plants.
Oh, it's so exciting in springtime
to see these baby plants starting to grow.
We promise to be careful, Grandpa.
Very good. Off you go, then.
[giggling]
Grandpa Pig's
chocolate egg hunt has begun.
Have you got time for a cup of tea,
Grandpa Pig?
Ho, ho, yes.
It will take them ages to find my eggs.
I've hidden them very well.
Here's an egg. [grunts]
Peppa has found a chocolate egg
in a plant pot.
Here's another egg. [squeaks]
Rebecca Rabbit has found a chocolate egg
hiding under a leafy bush.
Hooray, an egg for me. [trumpets]
Emily Elephant has found a chocolate egg
in the branches of a tree.
[sniffs]
I think I can smell chocolate.
Freddy Fox has a very good sense of smell.
Yes.
Freddy Fox has found a chocolate egg
in the middle of the birdbath.
[giggling]
Grandpa, Grandpa.
We found the chocolate eggs.
-It was really fun.
-But it was a bit easy.
It wasn't easy for the little ones.
George, Richard, and Edmond
haven't found any eggs.
[crying]
I wonder where the other eggs are.
-Ho-ho-ho!
-[grunts]
Chocky egg.
-Ha-ha-ha!
-[squeaks]
-[giggles]
-Ah.
Edmond, I think
there's something behind your ear.
[trumpets and giggles]
-Everyone has found a chocolate egg.
-[giggling]
[squeaks] What do we do now, Grandpa Pig?
Ha, ha! You eat them, of course.
-Hello, children.
-Granny, Granny.
We found all the chocolate eggs.
Well, where are they?
I can't see any eggs.
-[chuckles]
-They're in our tummies.
[Granny Pig] And 'round your mouths.
[all laugh]
Did Grandpa hide the eggs well?
No. We big ones found them easily.
But the little ones needed helping.
[all sigh]
George, Richard, and Edmond
don't like to be the littlest ones.
Don't worry.
There'll soon be even littler ones
in the garden.
[grunts] Oh, yes. The little babies.
It's so exciting.
Grandpa already told us
about the baby plants, Granny.
But it's not that exciting.
We're not talking about baby plants,
Peppa.
Oh. What are you talking about?
Let's go and see Jemima,
Vanessa, Sarah, and Neville.
They're chickens.
Yes, and they have eggs, too.
Can we eat them?
No, Freddy. These eggs are about to hatch.
[clucking]
Oh! We're just in time.
The baby chicks are hatching.
[peeping]
[in unison] Aww. Baby chicks.
[Granny Pig] Now the chicks have hatched,
it really is springtime.
Let's pretend to be baby chicks.
[imitating baby chickens]
♪ I'm a little chick
Singing cheep, cheep, cheep ♪
♪ I like to pick up food
With my beak, beak, beak ♪
♪ I've a fluffy yellow head
Some straw for my bed ♪
♪ And I jump up and down
Singing cheep, cheep, cheep ♪
[giggling]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her family have come
to the summer fete.
[Peppa and George giggle]
[grunts] Look, a display
of rescue vehicles.
Granddad Dog is showing his pickup truck.
[woofs] This is the sound
my pickup truck makes.
[horn blares]
Mommy Sheep is showing the fire engine.
[bleats] This is the sound
the fire engine makes.
[siren sounds]
And Miss Rabbit
is showing her rescue helicopter.
This is the sound my helicopter makes.
-[beeping]
-[voice] Helicopter reversing.
Helicopter reversing.
Would you like to go for a ride?
-Yes, please.
-[giggles]
Okay, hop in.
Oh, dear. There's no room for me.
Never mind. I'll watch from the ground.
Daddy Pig doesn't like heights.
Whee-hee! We're going up in the air.
-[grunts]
-Yes. It can go straight up.
Up!
It can go straight down.
[Peppa and George] Whee!
It can even loop the loop.
[Peppa giggling]
Poor Daddy. He's missing all the fun.
Yes, poor Daddy.
One ice cream, please.
Mm. That's nice.
Maybe we should land now.
[man on speaker] Emergency. Emergency.
Calling rescue helicopter.
I'm on my way.
You're in luck. We've got a job to do.
Mr. Bull is digging up the road.
Moo. Hello, Miss Rabbit.
I've got a big metal pipe
that needs lifting.
Okay, Mr. Bull.
How can you lift that big pipe?
With my big magnet.
[Peppa] Hooray!
What are you going to do with the pipe?
Um... I'm not really sure.
I know. I'll put it down here,
where someone can easily find it.
Now I can give you a lift home.
But what about Daddy?
[keypad beeps]
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Mommy Pig] Daddy Pig,
can you make your own way home?
Miss Rabbit is giving us a lift.
Okay.
[Peppa] Daddy, Daddy.
We went up and down, and round and round.
Ho, ho. I'm really sad
to have missed that.
See you back at home.
[tires screech]
Who put that pipe there?
I know. I'll take a shortcut.
Hmm. It's a bit muddy.
[engine sputters]
Come on, car. Daddy Pig needs to get home.
[engine revs]
Daddy Pig is stuck.
I'll ring for Granddad Dog's pickup truck.
[keypad beeps]
[phone rings]
[woofs] Hello. Breakdown recovery.
I'm stuck in the mud.
-Can you come and rescue me, please?
-Sorry, Daddy Pig,
I'm moving a big metal pipe
that some maniac has left in the road.
I'll pass you on
to the next rescue service.
[phone rings]
Hello. Fire service.
[Daddy Pig] I'm stuck in the mud.
Can you rescue me, please?
Sorry Daddy Pig,
I'm rescuing a tortoise
that's stuck up a tree.
Come down, Tiddles.
I don't know why you like climbing trees.
You're a tortoise.
[bleats] Don't worry, Daddy Pig,
I'll pass you on
to the highest rescue service in the land.
[helicopter whirring]
What's that noise?
Whoa!
I'm flying.
Miss Rabbit's helicopter
has rescued Daddy Pig.
Hooray!
Lucky Daddy gets a helicopter ride
after all.
Shall we show him
what my helicopter can do?
-[Peppa] Yes.
-[Mommy Pig] Yes.
It can go straight up.
Whoa!
It can go straight down.
It can even loop the loop.
[groaning]
Everyone likes going up and down
and round and round
in Miss Rabbit's helicopter.
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and George's cousins
are coming to visit today.
Mommy,
how long before Cousin Chloë is here?
Not long now, Peppa.
Baby Alexander is coming, too, remember?
Oh, babies cry all the time.
They're so noisy.
I'm sure Baby Alexander
won't be that noisy.
[crying]
What's that sound?
Is it a car alarm?
Is it a fire engine?
No, it's Baby Alexander.
[crying continues]
Hello, Peppa. Hello, George.
Hello, Cousin Chloë.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Uncle Pig.
Hello.
Hello, Aunty Pig.
You remember Baby Alexander,
don't you, Peppa?
Yes.
-[music playing]
-[Alexander giggling]
Are you staying for a few days?
No, this is what Alexander needs
for just one day.
Can't go anywhere
without all these baby things.
-Oh.
-Hello, Baby Alexander.
He can't talk, Peppa.
If he can't talk, then how do you
know what he wants?
We guess.
[cries]
I'm guessing he's hungry.
Peppa, would you like
to help feed Alexander?
Yes, please.
It is lunchtime for Baby Alexander.
Cousin Peppa is going to feed you today,
Alexander.
Here you are, baby.
-[groans]
-Oh.
Here it is.
-[groans]
-[scoffs]
-He keeps turning his head.
-[groans]
Feeding Baby Alexander is quite hard.
Watch this.
Here comes the airplane.
[makes whooping sound]
[laughs]
Alexander likes it if you pretend
the spoon is an airplane.
You have a go, Peppa.
[grunts] Here comes the airplane.
[makes babbling sound]
Open your mouth, and in through the doors.
Whoosh!
-Hooray!
[giggles] That was an airplane.
Can you say "airplane"?
I told you, he can't talk.
He hasn't even said his first word yet.
Peppa, do you remember
what your first word was?
-No.
-It was "mommy."
[grunts] I thought Peppa's first word
was "daddy."
No, "mommy."
What was George's first word?
Dinosaur.
George's first word was "dinosaur."
Somebody looks like they had a good lunch.
Yes.
Bath time I think.
Baby Alexander is having a bath.
[giggles]
This is Mr. Dinosaur.
Can you say "dinosaur"?
[babbles]
He can't talk, Peppa.
[grunts] But he will talk one day.
Then you'll know what he wants.
What do you want to do now, Alexander?
[babbles]
[grunts] I think he wants
to go for a walk.
He can't walk yet,
but he can go out in his buggy.
[grunts] That's a clever little buggy.
Yes. Five gears, mud guards,
and ABS as standard.
Blah, blah, blah.
That's how daddies talk.
-[coos]
-Alexander likes it when you talk, Peppa.
That's because I am very interesting.
[laughing]
This is the sky. Can you say "sky"?
[babbles]
The sky is where rain comes from.
Can you say "rain"?
[giggles]
Rain is good for ducks and plants,
and making muddy puddles.
Peppa has found a big muddy puddle.
[grunts] Look, Alexander,
I'm jumping up and down in a puddle.
[giggles]
[giggling]
[grunts] I love jumping
up and down in puddles.
Puddles.
[all] Ooh!
Alexander has said his first word.
Puddles.
[in unison] Hooray! Puddles!
And I taught him to say it.
Puddles.
[laughing]
[theme song playing]